Guide to the Consumer Reports Archives records RL.11772
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports Archives records
1924-2015 and undated
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Consumer Reports (Firm)
RL.11772
15.0 Linear Feet
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The Consumer Reports Archive was first established in 1972 as the Center for the Study of Consumer Movements. Collection includes correspondence, forms, photographs, policy and procedure statements and other printed materials that pertain to the operation support activities of the Consumer Union Archives. Included are files relating to archival administration and records management for the organization, reference requests and reference files relating to exhibit planning, Consumers Union and consumer movement history, and photocopied materials for individual research requests on various subjects. Organization resources include staff biographies; collection finding aids, indexes, and inventories; card and microfiche files. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Arrangement
Organized into the following series: Office Files; Collection Guides; Staff and Affiliate Biographies; and Reference Card Files.
Biographical / Historical
Consumer Reports is a product testing and consumer advocacy nonprofit organization based in Yonkers, N.Y., founded in 1936. The Consumer Reports Archive was first established in 1972 as the Center for the Study of Consumer Movements. It was staffed until 1981 when it closed due to recession-era finances. It re-opened on a part-time basis in 1986, largely to support Consumers Union's 50th anniversary activities. In 1987 the recommendations of a consultant led to the reorganization of the Archive to focus more narrowly on Consumers Union activities and staff.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Provenance
The Consumer Reports Archives records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2019.
Collection Overview
Collection includes correspondence, forms, photographs, policy and procedure statements and other printed materials that pertain to the operation support activities of the Consumer Union Archives. Included are files relating to archival administration and records management for the organization, reference requests and reference files relating to exhibit planning, Consumers Union and consumer movement history, and photocopied materials for individual research requests on various subjects. Organization resources include staff biographies; collection finding aids, indexes, and inventories; card and microfiche files. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History.
Consumer advocacy; John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History
- Office Files, 1924-2012 and undated; 1
  Scope and Contents
  Series includes files pertaining to the administration of the archives and Consumer Reports' records management program: donor relations and collection solicitations, forms, policies and procedures, historical photographs of the stacks and reference areas. Series also includes general reference files of material pertaining to consumer movement history, Consumers Union, exhibit planning, and the results of various research projects.
  - Administrative Files, 1949-2012 and undated; 1
    - Access policies--Photographs and artwork, undated (Box 1)
    - Accession forms, undated (Box 1)
    - Accession records, 1991-1996 (Box 1)
    - Appraisal procedures, undated (Box 1)
    - Archival Checklist (History Factory publication), 2001 (Box 1)
    - Archives access form, undated (Box 1)
    - Archives access policy, 1978-1981 (Box 1)
    - Archives action plans, 1987-1988 (Box 1)
    - Archives and Manuscript Security (SAA publication), 1977 (Box 1)
    - Archives background, undated (Box 1)
    - Archives description, 1989 (Box 1)
    - Archives floor plan, 1990 (Box 10)
    - Archives goals and objectives, 1994 (Box 1)
    - Archives history, 1987-2006 (Box 1)
    - Archives mission statement, undated (Box 1)
    - Archives planning strategies, 1990 (Box 1)
    - Archives priorities, 2009 (Box 1)
    - Archives progress reports, 1990-2009 (Box 1)
    - Archives reports, 1988-1995 (Box 1)
    - Archives shelving installation, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Archives statistics, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Archives taxonomy, undated (Box 1)
    - Archives taxonomy (record groups), 1991 and undated (Box 1)
    - Archives tour, 2008 (Box 1)
    - Archivist job descriptions, 2006 (Box 1)
    - Atop the consumer movement (Bill Falk profile of Consumers Union), 1978 (Box 10)
    - Book for visitors to CU (Florence Mason), 1959; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Care of archival materials, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Center for the Study of the Consumer Movement, 1979-1989 and undated (Box 1)
    - Check-out policy, 1988 (Box 1)
    - Collecting policies, 1978-2008; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Collection management, 2009-2010 (Box 1)
    - Consultant, 1990-1998 (Box 1)
    - Consumer education paper, undated (Box 1)
    - Consumer organizations supported by Consumers Union, undated (Box 1)
    - Consumers Association of Canada, 1995 (Box 1)
    - Consumer Reports--Helpful Hints wall calendar, 2005 (Box 1)
    - Consumer Reports (Images of America publication)--Archives reference copy, 2005 (Box 1)
    - Consumers Union library--Printed material, 1971-1993 (Box 1)
    - Consumers Union library--Subject guides, 1990-1992 (Box 1)
    - Corresponcence and miscellaneous, 1977-2012; 11 folders (Box 1)
    - Data access policy, 1977-1978 (Box 1)
    - Disaster planning, 1995-1999; 2 folders (Box 1)
    - Donation forms, undated (Box 1)
    - Donor file, 1973-1979 (Box 2)
    - Elizabeth Yakel (consultant), 1987 (Box 2)
    - Glossary of terms for CR publications, 2003 (Box 10)
    - International Organization of Consumer Unions (IOCU)/Consumers International, 1983-2006; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Inventory worksheet instructions and procedures, undated (Box 2)
    - Iron Mountain--Digitization, 2009-2011 (Box 2)
    - Iron Mountain--Inventories, 2006-2010 and undated; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Iron Mountain--Miscellaneous, 2010-2011 (Box 10)
      Includes: Audiovisual Collection spreadsheet; transmittal sheets
    - Iron Mountain--Papers retrieved and processed, undated (Box 2)
    - Iron Mountain--Transfer forms, 1990-1993 (Box 2)
    - Magazine scanning project, undated (Box 2)
    - Mariol Gallichio--Paper conservation project, 2001 (Box 2)
    - New acquisitions, 1985-1991 (Box 2)
    - Note pads (James Guest?), 2001-2005 (Box 2)
    - Outside researchers, 2008-2009 (Box 2)
    - Outside researchers--Inger Stole, 2008-2009; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Outside researchers--Jacqueline Hall, 2008 (Box 2)
    - Outside researchers--Shannon Clark, 2009 (Box 2)
    - Outside researchers--Signed access forms, 1991-2003 (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Building decoration project, 1992 (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Captions, 1991-1992 (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Documentation (William Hubbell photographs of Mount Vernon facility), undated (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Missing images, undated (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Negatives log, 1983-1991 (Box 2)
    - Photographs--On loan, 1998-2001 (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Returned, 1994-2000; 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Photographs--Stacks area, undated (Box 2)
    - Processing notes--David Pittle, 2005-2006 (Box 2)
    - Processing notes--James Mendenhall, 1972 (Box 2)
    - Processing notes--Joel Gurin, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Processing priorities, 2007 (Box 2)
    - Processing progress reports, 2006-2007 (Box 2)
    - Reader service report (James Snider), 1986 (Box 2)
    - Records management program, 1988-1999; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Records management program--Destruction reports, undated (Box 2)
    - Records management program--Retention schedule, 2001 (Box 2)
    - Records survey, 1978 (Box 2)
    - Records transfer forms, undated (Box 2)
    - Reference procedure, undated (Box 2)
    - Reference requests, 1994-2012; 3 folders (Box 2)
    - Report on the CU library, 1974 (Box 2)
    - Shainwald Archives Fellowship, 1975-2008 (Box 2)
    - Subversion/Communism, 1949-1954 (Box 2)
    - Teaching aids, undated (Box 2)
    - Testing--Archives reference copy, 1986 (Box 3)
    - Thesaurus of Consumer Terms--I. Classified Display, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Thesaurus of Consumer Terms--II. Alphabetically Structured Display, 1982 (Box 3)
    - Video transfers, 2001 (Box 3)
  - Consumer Movement History, 1927-2008 and undated; 2
    - General, 1927-1931 and undated (Box 3)
    - Barbara Burns/Diane McKaig, 1969 (Box 3)
    - Consumer Federation of America, 1977 (Box 3)
    - Consumers Club, 1927-1929 (Box 3)
    - Consumers League/New York Milk Committee, 1978 (Box 3)
    - Consumers League of New Jersey, 1979 (Box 3)
    - Consumers Research, 1951-1973 (Box 3)
    - Cooperative League of the USA--To Tell the Truth, 1969; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Corporation of Consumers' Research, 1931-1934 (Box 3)
    - Food and Drug Administration--50th anniversary of Food Additive Amendment, 2008 (Box 3)
    - Kansas State University Consumer Movement Archives, undated (Box 3)
    - League of Women Shoppers, 1936 (Box 3)
    - National Consumers League, 1958 and undated (Box 3)
    - No Country for Honest Men: The Origins of CU in the American Market Place (Norman Silber), 2008 (Box 3)
    - On Becoming a Consumer Spokesman (University of Wisconsin Extension program), 1972; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - St Louis Consumer Federation, 1970-1978 (Box 3)
    - They Made a Difference, 1980; 2 folders (Box 3)
    - U.S. Government proclamations, 1962-1993 (Box 3)
    - Your Money's Worth, undated (Box 3)
  - Consumers Union, 1936-2011 and undated; 3
    - 35th anniversary--Continuing Need to Discover the Truth, 1971 (Box 3)
    - 60th anniversary planning, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Advocacy offices, 1979-1999 (Box 3)
    - Awards, 1990-2000 (Box 3)
    - Board of Directors, 1972-1999 (Box 3)
    - Consumers Union reports, 1936-1939 (Box 3)
    - Contraceptive booklet press, 1941-1945 (Box 3)
    - Early Years Remembered, undated (Box 3)
    - Energy Policy Advocacy (A. Karim Ahmed), 1974 (Box 3)
    - Evaluation of location alternatives, 1971 (Box 3)
    - History, 1938-1999 and undated; 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Identity theft mailing, undated (Box 3)
    - Incorporation documents, 1936-1993 (Box 3)
    - Information Center, 1996 (Box 3)
    - Inside CU, 1989 (Box 3)
    - Internet policy, 1995 (Box 3)
    - Mount Vernon building history, 2011 (Box 3)
    - Organization charts, 1973-1994 and undated (Box 3)
    - Organization structure, 1936-1974 (Box 3)
    - Review, 2000 (Box 3)
    - Selling America's Kids, 1990 (Box 4)
    - Statistics, 1971-2006 (Box 4)
    - Strategic plans, 1993-2009; 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Washington office, 1972-1974 (Box 4)
    - Western Consumers Union, 1939-1974 (Box 4)
  - Exhibits, 1933-2009 and undated; 4
    - 1939 World's Fair, 1935-1998 (Box 4)
    - 50th anniversary--Andrea Scott notes, 1951-1985 (Box 4)
    - 60th anniversary, 1994-1996; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - 75th anniversary, 2008-2009; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Before the Start of CU, 1935 (Box 4)
    - Board of Directors, 1934-1992 (Box 4)
    - Communist Charges, 1933-1973 and undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Communist Charges--Compulsion the Key to Collectivism (National Physicians Committee), 1946 (Box 4)
    - Foreign Consumer Magazines, undated (Box 4)
    - Idea file, 1994 (Box 4)
    - Press Blackout, 1953 (Box 4)
    - Safety, 1937-1997 (Box 4)
    - Strike of 1935 (Box 4)
    - Then and Now, 2004-2008 (Box 4)
    - World War II, 1942-1970 (Box 4)
  - Oral History Project and Survey (donor solicitations), 1958-2010; 5
    - General, 1974-2010 (Box 4)
    - A.J. Isserman, 1965-1979 (Box 4)
    - Alexander Crosby, 1971-1978 (Box 4)
    - Board members, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Brookwood Labor College, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Erma Angevine, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Frank Pollock, 1978 (Box 4)
    - Harold Aaron, 1973-1979 (Box 4)
    - Harold Webber, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Helen Hall, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
    - Jerome Hellerstein, 1975-1979 (Box 4)
    - Marjorie East, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Inventories, 1977 (Box 4)
    - Meyer Parodnick, 1977-1979 (Box 4)
    - Miscellaneous, 1958-1977 (Box 4)
    - Sidney Margolius, 1972-1979 (Box 4)
    - Staff and others, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Stewart Lee, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
    - Stuart Chase, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
    - Sylvia Lane, 1978 (Box 4)
    - William Pabst, 1973-1979 (Box 4)
  - Research Projects, 1924-2003 and undated; 6
    - American Federation of Teachers, 1931-1941 (Box 4)
    - Bibliographies, undated; 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Can Openers, 1941-1987 (Box 4)
    - Cigarettes, undated (Box 4)
    - Civil Liberties Committee of Massachusetts, 1931-1976 (Box 4)
    - Consumerism, 1969-1998 (Box 4)
    - Dorothy Douglas, 1934-1968 (Box 4)
    - Home Front--Patriotism/World War II, 1941-1946 (Box 4)
    - Home Front--Post 9/11, 2002-2003 (Box 4)
    - Jerome Davis, 1935-1966 (Box 4)
    - Katherine Lumkin, 1932-1971 (Box 4)
    - League for Independent Political Action, 1929-1941 (Box 4)
    - Not acceptable products, 1942-1971 (Box 5)
    - Paul Douglas, 1924-1963 (Box 5)
    - Product safety, 1936-1971 (Box 5)
    - Ralph Harlow, 1932-1943 (Box 5)
    - Socialist Party, 1931-1943 (Box 5)
    - Toasters, 1939-1995 (Box 5)
- Collection Guides, 1936-2013 and undated; 2
  Series includes archives collection guides; stacks location guides, finding aids for individual collections, preliminary inventories of collections, and a variety of multi-year indexes to magazine articles.
  - Finding Aids, 1936-2013 and undated; 7
    - 16mm film log, undated (Box 5)
    - A.J. Isserman, 1978 (Box 5)
    - Adleaide Schulkind Frank, undated (Box 5)
      Papers on deposit at the Schlesinger Library
    - Archives finding aid, undated (Box 5)
    - Archives finding aid (binder), undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Archives finding aid with shelf locations, 2013; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Archive holdings, 2010; 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Arthur Kallett, undated (Box 5)
    - Audiovisual materials, undated (Box 5)
    - Audiovisual materials with CRTV News Feeds, 1992-1997 (Box 5)
    - Bibliography, undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Bibliography (Ulman), undated (Box 5)
    - Bibliography of consumer history, undated (Box 5)
    - Board of Directors meeting minutes, undated (Box 5)
    - Cassette and reel-to-reel tapes, undated; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Colston Warne, 1980, 1989; 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative, undated (Box 5)
    - Consumer Reports Index, 1936-1971; 6 folders (Box 5)
    - Consumer Reports Index, 1967-1993; 19 folders (Box 6)
    - Consumers International archives, undated (Box 6)
    - Dissertations, undated (Box 6)
    - "Econ" articles published in Consumer Reports 1955-1960 (Box 6)
    - Edward Brecher, undated (Box 6)
    - Edward Reich, undated (Box 6)
    - First Time Tested, undated (Box 6)
    - Florence Mason/IOCU, undated (Box 6)
    - Foreign publications, undated (Box 6)
    - George Brunn, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Guide to Documents of the Consumer Movement (National Catalog of Source Material), 1980 (Box 6)
    - Helen Canoyer, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Helen Nelson/Center for Consumer Affairs, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Henry Harap, undated (Box 6)
    - Index and articles on health care 1937-1994, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Index of Consumers Union legislative stands 1936-1973 (Box 6)
    - Index of Consumers Union statements on public interest matters 1935-1975, 1976, 1983; 3 folders (Box 6)
    - Index to Advocacy Office documents 1982-2001, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Index to Advocacy Office statements, 1982 (Box 6)
    - Index to Consumers Union News Digest 1977-1990, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Index to Penny Power 1984-1990 (Box 6)
    - Index to Questions of Health 1985-1989 (Box 6)
    - Inventory of Materials Contained in the Consumers Union Archive, 2007 (Box 6)
    - Irving Michelson, 1978 (Box 6)
    - James Mendenhall, 1978 (Box 6)
    - Last Time Published 1972-1992 (Box 6)
    - Last Time Published in Consumer Reports 1978-2003, 2009 (Box 6)
    - Last Time Tested 1967-1978 (Box 6)
    - Leland Gordon, undated (Box 6)
    - Master finding aid, undated (Box 6)
    - Meta-finding aid and how to find materials, 2010 (Box 6)
    - Morris Kaplan, 1978 (Box 6)
    - National Association of Consumers, undated (Box 6)
    - Paul Kern, undated (Box 6)
    - Persia Campbell, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Persia Campbell, 2011 (Box 10)
    - Photographs, undated (Box 7)
    - References in CU Library to CU, consumer movement, undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Sylvia Lane, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Weights and Measures Research Center/Leland Gordon, undated (Box 7)
    - William S. Taylor, undated (Box 7)
    - Zillions 1990-2000, 1998, 2010; 2 folders (Box 7)
  - Preliminary Inventories, 1972-2010 and undated; 8
    - General, undated (Box 7)
    - A.J. Isserman, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Arthur Kallett, undated (Box 7)
    - Audiovisual collections, 1995-2006; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Auto Center, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Books, 1994-2000 (Box 7)
    - Broadcast/Film Division, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Buying Guides, 2008 (Box 7)
    - Colston Warne, 1978-1997; 4 folders (Box 7)
    - Consumer-Farmer Milk Cooperative, 1979 and undated; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Consumer Federation of America, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Consumer Reports internal newsletters, undated (Box 7)
    - Consumer Reports publications, 2007-2008 (Box 7)
    - Consumers Union printed forms, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Design Department photographs, undated (Box 7)
    - Donal Dinwiddie, 1974 (Box 7)
    - Editorial Department, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Educational Services Division, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Edward Reich, undated (Box 7)
    - Executive Office, 2006 (Box 7)
    - Film and Video, 1994 and undated (Box 7)
    - Foreign Magazines, undated (Box 7)
    - Hallway cabinets, undated (Box 7)
    - Health advocacy (Gail Shearer, Washington office), 2009 (Box 7)
    - Helen Canoyer, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Helen Nelson, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Henry Harap, undated (Box 7)
    - Irving Michelson, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Joel Gurin, 2006 (Box 7)
    - Leland Gordon, undated (Box 7)
    - Materials contained in the Consumers Union archive, 2007 (Box 7)
    - Morris Kaplan, 1978 (Box 7)
    - National Association of Consumers, undated (Box 7)
    - Offsite records, 2007 (Box 7)
    - Paul Kern, 1972 (Box 7)
    - Periodicals, 1991 (Box 7)
    - Persia Campbell, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Personnel Department, 1979 (Box 7)
    - Photographers Office, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Promotion Department, undated (Box 7)
    - Records list, 2001 (Box 7)
    - Reel-to-reel tapes 1961-1980, 2006-2010; 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Sidney Shainwald, 1973 (Box 7)
    - Special publications, 1977 (Box 7)
    - Staff Information Services, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Sylvia Lane, 1978 (Box 7)
    - Technical Divisions, 1973 and undated (Box 7)
    - Vital records, 1998 (Box 7)
    - Warren Braren, 1975-1980 (Box 7)
    - Washington, D.C. advocacy office (Gail Shearer) 2000-2010 (Box 7)
    - Weights and Measures Research Center/Leland Gordon, 1979 (Box 7)
    - William S. Taylor, undated (Box 7)
- Staff and Affiliate Biographies, 1924-2015 and undated; 3
  Beginning in the mid-1970s, Consumers Union management initiated a project to compile biographical sketches of managerial staff. Around 1978, the Center for the Study of Consumer Movements (the Consumer Reports Archive) reached out to present and former staff and members of the Board of Directors for biographical information, invitations to participate in an oral history interview series, and solicitation for manuscript donations. Series includes correspondence, transcripts of recorded conversations, clippings, obituaries, speeches and other materials collected.
  - General, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Aaron, Harold, 1988 (Box 7)
  - Anderson, Kurt, 1946-1973 (Box 7)
  - Angevine, Erma, 1967-1979 (Box 7)
  - Bahr, Gladys, 1961-1970 and undated (Box 7)
  - Barrett, Stephen, 1974-1977 (Box 7)
  - Berberian, John, 1975 (Box 7)
  - Berliner, David C., 1978-1979 (Box 7)
  - Boards of Directors, 2001-2008 (Box 7)
  - Bookspan, Martin, 1979 (Box 7)
  - Bonner, Raymond T., 1975-1976 (Box 7)
  - Brady, Robert and Mildred, 1934-1994 (Box 7)
  - Brecher, Edward, 1963-1989 (Box 7)
  - Brooks, Thomas, 1975-1978 (Box 7)
  - Brown, Susan Jenkins, 1973 (Box 7)
  - Brunn, George, 1975-1978 (Box 8)
  - Bussey, William S., 1979 (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Persia, 1958-1972 (Box 8)
  - Campbell, Wallace, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Canoyer, Helen, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Carstens, Arthur, 1974-1978 (Box 8)
  - Carter, Gersuila, undated (Box 8)
  - Cavagnaro, Charles, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Chase, Stuart, 1924-1985 (Box 8)
  - Clark, Lincoln, 1974-1979 (Box 8)
  - Coles, Jessie V., 1978 (Box 8)
  - Coppock, Esther M., 1978 (Box 8)
  - Crooks, Lawrence, 1938-1977 (Box 8)
  - Cross, Hartley, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Cross, Richard, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Dinwiddie, Donal, 1978-1979 and undated (Box 8)
  - Edwards, Corwin D., 1974-1978 (Box 8)
  - Elliott, Harriet, 1970-1978 (Box 8)
  - Employee directory, 1994 (Box 8)
  - Ernyei, John, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Ernst, Morris, 1932-1936 (Box 8)
  - Fleischer, Henry, 1958 and undated (Box 8)
  - Florman, Monte, 2015 (Box 8)
  - Foreman, Carol Tucker, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Frankenfeld, Phil, 1973 and undated (Box 8)
  - Furman, Ira J., 1976 (Box 8)
  - Gamble, Philip L., 1978 (Box 8)
  - Gans, Helene, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Gibson, James J., 1978 (Box 8)
  - Gillaspy, Cathy, 1977-1978 (Box 8)
  - Gordon, Leland J., 1974-1987 (Box 8)
  - Gurin, Joel, 2005 (Box 8)
  - Haller, William, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Harap, Henry, 1924-1978; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Harris, Conrad, 1975 and undated (Box 8)
  - Hawes, Elizabeth, undated (Box 8)
  - Henle, Guy, 1973-1992 (Box 8)
  - Herrmann, Robert, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Hopkins, John S., 1979 (Box 8)
  - Horowitz, Laura, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Isserman, Abraham J. (A.J.), 1978-1989 (Box 8)
  - Johnson, Charles, undated (Box 8)
  - Jordan, Lynn, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Kallett, Arthur, 1932-2007; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Kaplan, Morris, 1948-1971 (Box 8)
  - Karpatkin, Rhoda, undated (Box 8)
  - Kern, Paul, undated (Box 8)
  - Keyserling, Mary D., 1987 and undated (Box 8)
  - Klein, Robert J., 1970-1993 (Box 8)
  - Kinsey, Jean, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Knauer, Virginia, 1974-1983 (Box 8)
  - Knoll, Robert D., 1975 (Box 8)
  - Kory, Judy, 1978 (Box 8)
  - Landau, Irwin, 1975-2015 (Box 8)
  - Landis, Benson Y., 1937 (Box 8)
  - Leers, Kate (Mrs. George Black), 1939-1974 (Box 8)
  - Leff, Jonathan, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Lever, Jack (E.J.), 1971-1972 (Box 8)
  - Lieberman, Trudy, 1995-1997 (Box 8)
  - MacColl, William A., 1975-1979 (Box 8)
  - Margolius, Sidney, 1940-1976 (Box 8)
  - Mason, Florence, 1939-1990; 4 folders (Box 8)
  - Masters, Dexter, 1938-1998 (Box 8)
  - Maynes, E. Scott, 1969-1978 (Box 8)
  - McCloskey, Gordon E., undated (Box 8)
  - McDonald, Grace, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Means, Gardiner C., 1978-1988 (Box 8)
  - Mendenhall, James E., 1938-1971 (Box 8)
  - Meyer, Louis B., 1978 (Box 8)
  - Michelson, Irving, 1952-2015 (Box 8)
  - Mohr, Lillian, 1978-1979 (Box 8)
  - Morris, Ruby Turner, 1969-1978 (Box 8)
  - Morse, Richard, 1970-2000; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Myerson, Bess, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1967-1989; 2 folders (Box 8)
  - Nader, Ralph, 1967-1979; 2 folders (Box 9)
  - Nelson, Helen, 1974-1995 (Box 9)
  - New staff/promotions notices, 1993-2010 (Box 9)
  - Newman, Sarah, 1978 (Box 9)
  - Nunn, William, 1929-1975 (Box 9)
  - Oxenfeldt, Alfred R., 1950 (Box 9)
  - Palmer, Dewey, 1937-1978 (Box 9)
  - Palmer, Frank L., 1971-1974 (Box 9)
  - Parodneck, Meyer, 1994 (Box 9)
  - Peterson, Esther, 1963-1995; 4 folders (Box 9)